(One Summer Day)
- Nice to see you. - Nice to see you all.
It's time to bring in the star of this week's Rainbow Live.
I've never had the chance to meet her in person.
But Kim Sook...
has been telling me about her for about six months.
- Really? - Sook said she was an amazing girl.
Sook said we had to invite her.
- I see. - So I strongly recommended her too.
She captured the hearts of many great actors and actresses.
- Her acting is superb. - Right.
It's Actress Ryu Hye Young.
- Welcome. - Oh, my.
I'm finally meeting her in person.
- We're meeting her in person. - That's right.
Oh, my.
- Hello. - Hello.
(She left a strong impression on the viewers...)
(as the grumpy, but intelligent girl in "Reply 1988.")
Hey. Here's the thing.
(She perfectly pulled off all of her characters.)
(Always the scene-stealer...)
(who caught the viewers' attention regardless of her roles)
Hello. I've been living alone for 11 years.
I'm Actress Ryu Hye Young.
Eleven years?
(Welcome to the show.)
- This is your first time here. - Yes.
Could you tell us how it feels to be here?
Well, the studio is smaller than I expected.
It makes me feel cozy that I could talk more comfortably here.
- Actually, - I'm looking forward to it.
- before you arrived, - Yes.
Sung Hwan said...
- he was a huge fan. - Well...
- Really? - Yes.
I saw you in the short film and the independent film as well.
My voice is shaking.
I've been a huge fan for a long time.
Thank you.
Where are you looking at?
People might think you're my fan.
It's my first time meeting Hye Young in person too.
I didn't know you were this stylish.
I had no idea you had such a cool vibe.
She's famous among fashion enthusiasts.
- Really? - Yes.
- She's very fashionable. - She is...
Did you cut your own hair?
I didn't cut it myself.
But I did tell them how I wanted it to be cut.
- They took your feedback. - Yes.
- You have a wild hairstyle. - Are you crazy?
I like wild vibes.
All right. Let's check out her clips together.
(A Weird Adult)
"A weird adult?"
(It's quiet and dark in the room.)
- You have the blackout curtains. - Yes.
I wake up...
immediately when there's even a tiny bit of sunlight.
- You're a light sleeper. - I love those curtains.
My room has to be completely dark like yours.
(Tossing and turning)
(She turns on her tablet PC, not the light at 11:13am.)
(Yawning)
- Everyone... - She's watching YouTube.
- As soon as you wake up? - Yes. It's fixed.
- I see. I know what it is. - It must be the holder.
- It's the holder. - It is.
(Wide awake)
Hello.
I've been living alone for 11 years now.
I'm Actress Ryu Hye Young.
(Hye Young starts her day by watching a video.)
(Sluggish)
(She's on her phone.)
(Ringing)
Have you traveled abroad recently?
- What? - Did something break down?
It's been ages since I traveled abroad.
- It's an app. - An app?
It helps me study.
Is it Duolingo?
- I'm on Duolingo and Speak. - I see. You use Speak.
When did you start learning English?
It's been two years...
since I...
No.
I've been learning English for two years.
(Ding)
(She studies Japanese after English.)
- What? - Japanese?
You're also studying Japanese.
- You start the next one right away. - I start it right away.
I'm on the next app.
- As soon as you wake up? - Two languages?
(Focused on learning languages while lying on her bed)
I wanted to do at least one thing a day...
that I could compliment myself for.
Maybe, I wanted to feel a sense of achievement...
from doing something small like that.
(Smiling)
- Once you feel it, - Right.
- you get addicted to that feeling. - It's an...
- addiction indeed. - Right.
(She hasn't budged an inch on her bed after waking up.)
(She kept studying for about an hour.)
She might spend her entire day on her bed.
(She's studying hard in her dark room.)
Why is this so hard?
(On a 196-day streak)
I've been studying for 196 consecutive days.
- For 196 days? - Yes.
- It's been 196 days so far. - You're very persistent.
It's not easy to collect the flame stickers.
(Getting up)
You came up with a really nice daily routine.
- She didn't go back to sleep. - She really keeps this up.
Right. I can see that she does this every day.
She's very diligent.
(She gets out of her bed after studying languages.)
(Tossing)
(Hye Young leaves her dark bedroom at last.)
No.
All right.
My gosh. You don't have any sunlight in your house.
They are also blackout curtains.
My gosh.
(She moves around in the dark.)
I've been living in this house for a year and a half now.
I renovated the house a bit.
I decorated the house to suit my style.
It's my cozy little house.
- Your house has a simple look. - Yes.
This house has white floors and wooden molding.
- My gosh. - I wanted some decorative props.
Colorful decor...
looked pretty good in this house.
- What a cute place. - It's got a minimalistic charm too.
You must like toy figurines.
I can never say no to cute things.
- They're so cute. - They're hard to say no to.
This is a very old apartment.
So I started to bring in more colors to this house.
This house bears the marks of time.
- That's how it used to look before? - Yes.
I kept the renovation to the minimum.
It looks like a brand-new house.
(An old-fashioned kitchen)
- Wait, you did it yourself? - Yes, I did.
(She replaced it with a clean stainless table.)
- Gosh. That will stay clean. - She has an eye for this.
I measured the size and custom-ordered the plate.
- Did she put it over? - I placed it over the table.
- You did? - Yes, I could do that.
Right.
Stainless steel, wood, and white...
were the core themes.
I kept the decoration work to the minimum.
How neat.
- The house suits you. - Right.
- Really? Thank you. - The house suits your image.
(Walking over)
Get some sunlight.
(She opens the curtain just slightly.)
- My gosh. - What?
- Do you have a cat? - What's going on?
- Why did you stop growing? - What?
(It's Hye Young's plant.)
- You have a plant. - Yes.
How beautiful. Get some sunlight. Only you should get the sunlight.
(A tiny gap)
(She timidly opens it a little more.)
You drew them just enough...
- for the plant to get sunlight. - Yes.
I only let my plant get some sunlight.
Is there a reason you don't want any sunlight in your house?
It started when I was filming "Reply 1988."
I suddenly got so much attention from the public.
I realized that my words...
- had power. - I see.
That's when I realized it.
That made me be more careful with my words.
I got more timid...
- at meeting people. - You got timid. I see.
- I get scared easily. - Really?
- You suddenly felt anxious. - Yes.
I usually keep the curtains closed due to my anxiety too.
(Only her plant is allowed to get sunlight.)
Why did you stop growing? Do you want more water?
(Why did you stop growing? Do you want more water?)
- What are you doing? - You were growing.
(She quickly checks for moisture with bare hands.)
(I think you have enough water.)
Why did you stop?
Please answer me.
Yes, I hear some people do this.
They talk to their plant when they wake up.
- You have to. - You have to do that.
They're also alive. So they can understand everything.
You can do this, right?
I don't know much about plants.
I asked my expert friends.
I trimmed my plant. Afterward, it started to grow again.
My plant needs some cheering.
Only that one gets sunlight.
- Yes. - I trimmed it.
I say hello to my plant every day.
I say goodnight to it...
- before going to sleep. - Yes.
"You can do this. We're in this together."
"We're one."
"If you die, I die too." I'd say things like that.
This is the longest plant I've ever had without killing it.
(More affectionate for her longest-surviving plant)
How beautiful.
(After checking up on her plant,)
(she goes to the dressing room.)
(Pulling)
(Plopping down)
They're toe socks.
(Popping out)
I started to wear...
toe socks for my foot health.
People said they were better for my feet, so I tried them on.
And I liked them.
- That's a good thing. - Toe socks are comfortable for me.
- Are you wearing them today? - Actually, I'm wearing...
- Toe socks. - toe socks.
- You really are. - Toe socks
- My gosh. - You really are. So cute.
They look stylish because you're wearing them.
- Hey, if... - Being able to...
move our toes individually...
is more beneficial to our foot health.
(With her warm feet,)
(she goes to the living room.)
(She fixes her sitting posture.)
(Focused)
Oh, my.
- What is it? - Will she play music?
I can't predict what she'll do next.
(She stares at something with intense focus.)
No.
- What is it? - It's 3.25 percent...
lactose-free milk.
I like watching housewives' vlog videos.
A lot of their vlog videos show their daily lives.
- Housewives' vlog videos? - Yes.
They're super popular.
Watching other people go on with their ordinary lives...
gives me a huge sense of stability.
I seek peacefulness...
from ordinary day-to-day lives.
That's how I am.
- They give a sense of comfort. - Yes.
So I keep watching housewives' vlog videos.
I think she needs to hire a helper.
That part is too weak.
(She's completely in sync with the housewife.)
(She stays in her seat without moving an inch.)
I bet you learn a lot...
- from those videos. - I learn so much.
You can get so many tips from the videos.
- The lifestyle tips. - Seriously.
(Peacefully learning lifestyle tips)
No way.
Hold on.
- Okay. Wait. - I just saw him.
My son. Okay.
It's Wilson.
(Wilson greets Hye Young.)
(Observing)
You look scary.
- His eyes are protruding a lot. - Wilson looks a bit slim.
- You do. - His eyes can be scary.
If it doesn't work, you can call a plumber.
Why did you put your hand up?
Because Wilson keeps staring at her.
- It's like you're being stared at. - I see.
What?
(Completely blocking Wilson's gaze)
(As she feels super shy around Wilson,)
(she focuses on the cooking process in the vlog video.)
(Intrigued)
I should eat too.
(She pauses the video.)
(Grabbing)
(Her breakfast ingredient is a loaf of bread.)
(I should toast it to make it crispy.)
(Like an avid viewer of housewives' vlog videos,)
(she zips up the leftover bread in a sealable bag.)
(The bread is toasted to a golden brown.)
It's hot.
Bread tastes so good with some peanut butter.
Gosh, no way. It's peanut butter.
I love it.
Add some strawberry jam. Yes.
- "Yes." - Gosh, there you go.
- This hits the spot. - You added a lot.
(This is what I'm talking about.)
(Her jammy breakfast is ready.)
This is crazy. I should clean up after I eat.
(Let me eat this right away.)
(Having her sacred first bite while kneeling down)
(This is it.)
(Humming)
(Salivating)
It's leaking, right?
(A simple, but happy meal)
- That's your breakfast, right? - Yes.
- That's... - It's my breakfast.
I even named it.
- The Greed Toast. - The Greed Toast?
- What greed? - Where's the greed?
(Where's the greed?)
- I greedily added the jam. - I see.
- I tend to add a lot of jam... - Just one...
to the point that having two slices...
- would make me feel guilty. - Don't think like that.
- Don't think that. - I can only have it for breakfast.
- Give yourself a break. - The guilty ones are looking.
- Don't think that. - They're clearly guilty.
(If overeating is a sin, that makes us sinners already.)
- Don't listen to the evil ones. - You can't do that to bread.
- You can't do that. - That's not right.
(Stopping)
(I should drink something.)
(Her neatly organized fridge...)
(is full of soda cans?)
The lemon-lime soda is my favorite drink.
I drink 3 to 4 cans a day.
How should I put it?
I personally find the flavor balance perfect.
The levels of carbonation,
sweetness,
and fragrance are perfectly balanced.
It's just perfect for my taste.
It's refreshing, I guess.
That's why when I'm abroad,
I miss this brand's soda more than kimchi.
(She grabs the drink without thinking about it.)
I have no choice.
(Excited)
How do you do that?
(Gulping down the cool drink)
- My gosh, yes. It's refreshing. - Yes. It's so good.
(She quenches her thirst with the perfectly-balanced drink.)
(She eats up the last piece.)
(Grabbing)
- You read books too? - Yes. I do a bit of reading.
(While playing the vlog video in the background,)
(she calmly begins reading a book.)
- You do everything at the table. - That's my spot.
It's the entire radius of your activity.
(She's become one with her companion chair.)
(She's focused on her reading for some time.)
(She continues reading her book for an hour.)
(Let me clean up now.)
(She places the plates in the kitchen sink.)
(Why is she going into the dressing room?)
Hold on. Leggings.
(She grabs leggings.)
Is she going out?
(She also grabs a windbreaker.)
With these...
- She's going to exercise. - She'll exercise.
(Putting on the windbreaker first)
(She grabs a handkerchief to wipe sweat.)
(She's fully geared up with a hat and sunglasses.)
(She gets ready with determination and goes out.)
(Stretching)
(She stretches her wrists first.)
She looks like a track and field athlete.
- Look at her. - She might start doing high jumps.
- Gosh. - My gosh. She can stretch so well.
I run about 300km every month.
- Yes. - I have a friend who never runs.
He has the same physique.
But he can run faster.
- Maybe, she's an avid runner. - She's on a different level.
You don't know that yet. We have to watch to find out.
I can't wait to see her run.
Let's do this.
(Stretching like a pro)
She has the same physique of Kenyan runners.
- Definitely. - Kenyan runners?
- You could run fast... - I'll start the timer.
- with those legs. - Right.
Let's go.
(Turning on her smartwatch)
Right away?
Seeing how she's fully geared up, I don't think she's an avid runner.
- She has to be good at running. - She has to be good at it.
(It's time for Hye Young to show them her true skills.)
I've been running for three years.
She's been running for a long time.
I ran 2 of the 10km marathons last year.
So I completed both runs and received medals.
So that's what I've accomplished.
Kian84 was right.
(She's light on her feet from the start.)
Gosh, the weather is so good.
(Gentle)
- She's one of us. - I told you.
- Wait. - What?
(She's one of us.)
Welcome to our crew.
- You should just walk then. - I knew it!
- See? - You should join the Fun Run.
She's fully geared up.
- She couldn't have been good at it. - Absolutely.
I was excited when she said she'd been running for three years.
(Jogging lightly)
(Gently running with her full gear on)
My pace...
- She's thinking about that now? - Why is she checking that?
Why am I running so fast?
- Wait. - This is fast? No.
This is weird.
(I'm feeling pretty good today.)
- Walking is faster. - His walking is faster.
She's just like me.
(Toddling)
It's called slow running.
It's a super popular style of running these days.
- It takes 9 minutes to run 1km. - It takes 9 minutes?
That's the set pace.
Make sure your toes are touching the ground.
- There you go. - This is running.
- I taught it to Ju Seung. - You're right.
- It's the video I hate watching. - The shock...
It's about how short your steps are,
how you move your arms,
and which part of your foot hits the ground first.
I must run while thinking about all these things.
Then I can run slowly...
- and finish 1km in 9 minutes. - She's spot on.
Slow running seems easy.
But it's a difficult exercise.
If you run without thinking, you finish 1km in 7 minutes.
- That's not good at all. - Right.
And it messes up your posture.
- Right. - It ruins your joints too.
(She runs carefully to maintain her pace.)
(Zooming by)
Oh, my gosh.
I thought that would be her pace.
You can't give in to fast runners like him.
There's no need to do that.
- What about when you did 10km runs? - Yes.
Did you run as fast as you could?
I ran as fast as I could.
- You did. - I tried to finish 1km...
in seven minutes at the runs.
Didn't you regret that a lot?
I regretted it so much.
(You bet I did.)
- Seriously. - She should join the Fun Run.
Seriously.
- You've got a new member. - Look at him.
The 10km runs were so challenging for me.
- I love it. - I had a shoot the next day.
- Right. Exactly. - I almost died.
- Really? - It affected your work.
But I survived.
- Right. But... - That's why...
I tried it again.
Here's the thing. I thought...
you'd have energy left after finishing the runs.
- No. - I guess not.
- I thought I was going to die. - So...
- I had sleep paralysis too. - your crew...
(I had sleep paralysis too.)
- You have weak energy. - People run to stay healthy.
- My energy is very weak. - So...
- Indeed. - physique alone doesn't tell us...
- whether you're a good runner. - Never.
- I guess she's an exception. - It can't affect your job.
It's okay as long as I get there no matter how slow I am.
I don't need to compare myself to them.
Your skin will sag if you run fast anyway.
There's no need to run fast.
Gosh, the weather is amazing.
(I run in my own way.)
(So what if I'm slow like a tortoise?)
(It's fine as long as I get there!)
I'm running at a ten-minute pace. Good.
- For slow running, - Slow down.
my heart rate should be...
- between 130 and 140. - Right.
I must run...
- while maintaining the heart rate. - Right.
- It builds cardiovascular strength. - It's at 130 when you run...
(He has a lot to say, but won't.)
Hey, puppy. Isn't it hot?
Isn't it really hot? Oh, no.
It's so hot.
(She has enough energy to say hello to the puppy.)
She just needs to run a little bit faster.
- She doesn't want to! - Gosh.
- If she does... - Just a little bit faster.
If she does, it affects her job.
It does affect my job.
I'm here.
Great. I got here super fast.
(There's a pedestrian overpass.)
Pedestrian overpasses are tough.
(She must maintain her pace.)
There are stairs.
(A staircase is next to the elevator.)
- She should take the elevator. - No, the stairs.
(Which route will she choose?)
There are stairs.
(The overpass has an elevator and a staircase.)
- She should take the elevator. - No, the stairs.
(- She should take the elevator. - No, the stairs.)
I should be okay with the stairs, right?
What?
(She's taking the elevator.)
(We knew it!)
(A round of applause)
- Bravo. - Nice.
Yes!
- What? - People must rest.
If you're going to take it easy, just stay home. Why come out?
It's better than doing nothing.
- I'm getting vitamin D. - Of course.
Why do you think they built an elevator there?
- Right. - There's a reason for it.
- Of course. - Yes.
(Happy)
- She's back to running again. - She's running.
(She's on the overpass in no time.)
(An elevator and a staircase are on the other side.)
I'm sure she can handle the stairs going down.
(Thinking)
I should take a break in the elevator.
Right!
Going down stairs is more dangerous.
- Going down stairs... - Elevators are better.
- is straining on my knees. - It could strain your joints.
- My knees might get busted. - Of course.
You always say it strains your joints.
When you go down stairs,
it strains your joints.
- Yes. That's true. - That's how it is.
(Let me start running again.)
She's so excited that...
- Yes. - she can't stop dancing.
Ever since I started slow running regularly,
I can feel that my fitness has improved.
I'm here at Yongsan Station.
(She finally arrives at Yongsan Station.)
I'm here.
My pace is...
at 9 minutes and 48 seconds. It's perfect.
You might not know, but I tried so hard to stay focused on the run.
That was a long run, though.
This is the charm of slow running.
(I did it again.)
Great.
(She is going somewhere in a good mood.)
You know what?
More people are leaning...
- toward the Fun Run now. - Of course.
Here's the thing about the Fun Run tribe.
Once we finish our run,
- we never run afterward. - The Fun Run tribe?
- She's standing there. - Right. I'm just standing.
- The Fun Run tribe? - You made it up.
- The Fun Run tribe. - What's that?
- We're shy runners. - You know what?
They had been hiding because they were shy.
They started to come out now.
- Who made that happen? - Right.
Be confident.
- Look how confident I look. - Great.
(Hye Young confidently comes up to the shopping mall.)
(Big strides)
I see. Will she eat some food?
- I know where you're going. - She did a Fun Run.
- So you know? - Yes. Of course.
- The food court? - See?
Where is she going?
(She arrives at a gacha shop.)
- My gosh. - It's a gacha shop.
- I see. - The capsule vending machines.
- Yes. - I didn't know she liked them.
(A place where you can draw cute dolls)
Actually, the thing is,
I can never say no to cute things.
When I see something cute,
I just can't help it.
(So I'm here to check out cute dolls.)
(Looking around)
Please be here. There are so many machines here.
I found it!
No way! I must have it.
- I absolutely must have it. - mojojojo?
Yes. I'm obsessed...
- with mojojojo these days. - So cute.
mojojojo?
"Press the price button to start."
- Please insert your credit card. - Okay.
(Let's get a toy.)
Please. I want to get Matcha.
- I wanted the green one. - Matcha.
Is it done? It's done.
Please.
Come on out already. Let's see.
Whatever it is...
- Do you get a toy at random? - Yes, I get one at random.
You get one at random.
Please let it be Matcha.
Matcha.
(Opening)
- What is it? - It's okay.
- Pinky. - Pinky.
It's okay. It's cute.
It's so cute.
- Cute things drive me insane. - How is it so tiny?
It's okay. It doesn't have to be Matcha.
I just don't want this one.
Please let it be Bluebell or Matcha.
Please.
(The random dopamine party starts.)
It's blue.
(She gets a dopamine rush.)
It's my second favorite one.
It's so cute, isn't it?
Shall I get one of these? They're otters.
I want to know how much it is since she keeps getting the toys.
- Seven dollars. - The numbers add up.
- It's expensive. - It's pretty expensive.
- Seven dollars? - She is obsessed with cute things.
It's the price of her happiness.
The transaction has been completed.
Please.
She looks so excited.
- If it makes her that happy, - So cute!
- it's worth the money. - I'm so excited.
Hold on. What's this?
Yes, this is it! This is dopamine.
Seeing cute things makes me lose my reason.
But since I don't do it every day, it's okay.
I can rationalize my spending that way.
I've grown into a strange adult.
It was a great acquisition.
(Feeling satisfied, she heads back outside.)
(Stretching)
(Shall I keep going?)
I guess she'll run again.
- That's right. - She needs to take a taxi.
- Will she run again? - My goodness.
It's perfectly doable to run 4km.
It's hard to run even 3km.
She needs to take a taxi.
(She solemnly pulls up her socks.)
She'll run again.
- That's it! - Nice!
(She chose to take a taxi.)
- She did as I expected. - She is like us.
- She is like us. - She is like us.
The remaining distance was 3.78km.
- That's right. - And since I had to go back,
- I would've run nearly 8km. - No.
- Good thinking. - Then...
- how would I wake up the next day? - It's only 7km.
- Running more makes you drowsy. - That's right.
- It's too much. - I might fail to go home.
That's right.
- I'll hit the road. - Okay.
I got so many good toys.
- At least she tried it. - Exactly.
- At least she tried it. - I did run.
- That's right. - I ran nearly 4km.
(With a sense of accomplishment,)
(she arrives home in a taxi.)
The acquired toys of the day.
The last one I got is so cute.
It looks so dumb. It's so cute.
(The figurines satisfy her.)
- They look cute together. - They're the best.
- They're cute, right? - Yes.
- They look cute together. - I see.
That's why people collect them.
(She puts her clothes back in place.)
Weren't you sweating after exercising?
I sweated because of the hot weather,
not because of the run.
- You don't sweat much. - Since I ran slowly...
You didn't sweat at all during the Fun Run!
- He bought a blanket. - He felt cold...
and bought a blanket.
Your clothes stay as dry as they've been in the dryer.
That's right.
(Rushing over)
(She takes a quick shower.)
(Sprawled over)
(Gosh, I feel so refreshed.)
(Reaching)
My grandpa is exactly like that.
- Is the delivery complete? - Three times a week...
- What is it? - How did it arrive so fast?
- What? - She ordered something.
- You'll eat something, right? - Of course.
That's good. I almost felt emotional distance.
(Grabbing)
- It's heavy. That's nice. - What?
I have a good feeling about this.
(She sits on her chair with the heavy bag.)
- Raw fish? - My goodness.
- You like raw fish. - Raw fish.
I ordered raw flathead grey mullet.
Mullet is tasty.
It's tasty.
I must eat protein...
after exercising.
(Salivating)
I'm salivating.
I need to cook it.
(She stops salivating and heads to the kitchen.)
(She takes something out of the fridge.)
(Picking up)
(Cutting)
(She cuts lettuce first.)
(Then she expertly cuts chili peppers and perilla leaves.)
(She adds a bowl of rice.)
I'm obsessed with raw fish bibimbap these days.
I eat it four times a week.
But if I order raw fish bibimbap,
it doesn't have much raw fish.
- That's right. - It's like that.
So I order a plate of raw fish...
- and make raw fish bibimbap. - I see.
- Then you get a lot of raw fish. - Yes.
- That's a good idea. - I want to add a lot of raw fish.
(Salivating)
All right.
Good. It looks so tasty.
(Dipping)
- I try a piece as it is. - The first piece. That's right.
(She tries a piece of raw fish as it is.)
(Dipping)
She eats with gusto.
It was crunchy and chewy. It was so tasty.
(Pulling)
(Picking up a heap)
- My goodness. - Oh, my.
- It's time to add raw fish. - You keep the pieces big.
It's time to add raw fish.
(She puts big pieces of raw fish on the top.)
(Gulping)
(Then she adds chojang.)
Let's eat as much as I want.
(She mixes in as much as she wants.)
- It's half rice and half raw fish. - Half rice and half raw fish.
(The do-it-yourself raw fish bibimbap is complete.)
(She takes a big spoonful.)
(Impressed)
She eats with so much gusto.
(Half rice, half raw fish is the perfect ratio!)
(There is no greater happiness.)
(Getting up)
(She brings something in the most natural way.)
You really like that soda.
How could you not drink it when you eat raw fish bibimbap?
I agree.
(Opening)
(She drinks her second can of soda in a day.)
(It's the best for cleansing the palate.)
(My goodness)
I know the taste...
of soda after eating food.
- It makes anything go down. - That's right.
It's so refreshing.
(Eating)
(With the refreshed palate)
(Protein)
She eats with gusto.
- She eats with gusto. - She does.
- She eats naturally. - How nice.
- She takes big spoonfuls. - I absolutely love tasty food.
I eat with gusto.
(It's so tasty.)
(She finishes the last spoonful.)
- That was great. - Look at the raw fish.
She finished it.
(Now that I'm done, I should clean up.)
(Washing the dishes)
(Shaking off the water)
She cleans up after herself and scrubs the dishes.
It makes me feel good.
- When they're squeaky clean... - It's a way of treating yourself.
(She heads back to her chair after washing the dishes.)
(Picking up)
(Opening)
Is she drinking another can of soda?
(Fascinated)
(It's the third can of the day.)
(My goodness)
(It's always refreshing.)
(Grabbing)
All right.
(She opens a notebook.)
I need to write today's journal entry.
- She keeps a journal. - A journal.
Let's do this.
There is a passageway...
(She goes over the day in front of the white paper.)
(Writing)
I've written a journal entry daily for about five years.
I began because I was struggling emotionally.
There was...
a time I couldn't even sit still at home...
due to anxiety.
But whenever I wrote something,
I could sit still.
- She does everything consistently. - Daily?
She is really good at doing things daily.
Being an actor requires a lot of waiting.
That's right.
So coming up with a routine and sticking to it...
might help with mental health.
I wanted to share that with everyone.
I use this time to understand...
and comfort myself.
The short period of time that lasts 5 to 10 minutes...
piles up daily.
I almost think it's thanks to that time...
that I've transformed into someone...
- active. - Right.
It's really fascinating that everyone has...
their own time.
I didn't have courage.
I didn't have money. I didn't have confidence.
I didn't have anything.
I was in despair.
One day, I washed up and looked in the mirror.
I saw a woman who was...
able-bodied and healthy before my eyes.
"You're pretty, beautiful,"
"healthy, and young."
"Why on earth would you hide?"
"Go out there and do everything you want."
- "Live your life however you want." - That's right.
"Do whatever you want."
The words I said to myself...
piled up and gave me strength.
These days, I have...
less fear regarding...
the world.
Now, I'm like, "Let's just try it. Let's just do it."
In the movies and dramas, she always plays a character...
that's capable and perfect.
But in real life,
she is like a younger sister. Seriously.
She is a junior I want to keep inviting out.
To be honest, Mi Ran...
invited me out for years.
But I couldn't bring myself to say yes.
- I sent a lengthy reply to say no. - You felt bad.
Despite that, she always invited me out.
She always invited me to go on a trip or something.
But I made up my mind one day and replied,
- "Okay. I'd like to go." - Right.
That was when I began to open up.
Today, I ran...
extremely slowly.
When people pass by me,
I become anxious and pick up my pace at times.
But there is no need to do that.
- I just need to go at my pace. - That's right.
Now that the arduous time is in the past,
I feel like I've grown a lot.
(The season I love the most is passing quickly.)
(But I'll remember how I ran today while enjoying springtime.)
(Nothing eventful happened, and it was the best day.)
(A Very Ordinary Day)
We enjoyed the video.
(Hye Young's daily life leaves lingering emotions.)
It was your first time...
- watching your daily life. - Yes.
- How was it? - I should drink less soda.
- Why do I drink so much of it? - Is that the first thought?
- Yes. Why do I drink so much of it? - You drink it all the time.
It must be an addiction.
Many moments were memorable.
- That's right. - Yes.
Was the sudden attention from people intimidating?
It was so scary.
Some types of attention were good,
but they came with the bad types of attention.
I wasn't prepared.
Perhaps it wasn't my time.
I had that thought.
I see.
The thing is, your ability to feel emotions in a way...
that is more delicate,
- detailed, and beautiful... - That's right.
- makes you prone to anxiety. - That's right.
The ability to feel what other people can't feel...
- is a blessing. - For an actor, it's a blessing.
- I thought she was strong. - I know.
She seems more soft-hearted now.
- She reminds me of a snail. - I see.
- She hides in her house. - A snail.
I did that in the past.
- Now, I'm a slug. - Yes.
A slug.
- I got rid of the house. - A slug.
- From a snail... - Yes, I got rid of the house.
- She doesn't hide. - So that I'd have no place to hide,
I threw away the house.
- I kept hiding in it. - That's good.
"So what if I have a lot of fear? I can't do anything about it."
- That's right. - That's my attitude now.
I try to focus on each and every day...
these days.
Although I worry,
- I don't go beyond tomorrow. - That's right.
Although I plan,
- I don't go beyond tomorrow. - Good.
I live each and every day...
- with that thought. - I see.
We'll root for your courageous daily life.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Seriously.
- Welcome. - All right.
Seon Min visited after a long hiatus after the Rainbow Live.
How have you been?
- My life changed after the show. - How did it change?
People around me only saw me as a YouTuber.
Now, I'm a celebrity...
- who stars on major TV channels. - Major TV channels.
Men and women who would've passed by me in the neighborhood...
recognize me now.
- I'm so grateful. - You've become popular.
Your videos had so many views on the official YouTube channel.
That's right.
I'm thankful that a video got over three million views.
(His video got over 3.2 million views.)
Thank you.
- It's my first time meeting him. - Yes.
I'm such a huge fan.
I'm so happy right now.
- Thank you. - Judging from what I've seen,
- he totally eats like us. - He eats like us. Seriously.
- I love eating. - Seriously.
- For goodness' sake. - This is great.
It's unfair to have three big eaters at once.
I know.
- What? - Let's stick to ourselves.
- Seriously. - Please invite me.
- That's a great idea. - I'm a huge fan.
(Oh, Victory for Korea)
Oh, Korea.
(CODE KUNST is sleeping in the bright bedroom.)
- My goodness. - It has been a while...
to see his house.
(Blinking)
Why are you sleeping upside down?
Since the sun rises too early,
I can't get much sleep otherwise.
(The bright sun makes him wake up feeling groggy.)
Siru.
(Come here.)
(Rushing over)
So cute.
He is like a dog.
(After greeting Siru in the morning)
It's hot.
It's so hot these days.
All right.
- What's that? - Is that a fan?
- It looks so pretty. - It works as a fan.
It resembles a hammerhead shark.
(Let's turn on the fan.)
(Pressing the remote)
(Cool wind comes out.)
The wind travels far.
It's cool.
It's a paradise.
(Blinking)
(He opens his drooping eyes and gets up.)
It's 8:15am.
- Wait. Why did you get up so early? - What has gotten into you?
(It's the miracle morning.)
(Grabbing his phone)
(Typing)
How did they fail to score?
- Score? - Is it that hard?
Is it that hard?
My goodness.
He is watching soccer.
Three players got sent off?
- Mexico versus South Africa. - Mexico versus South Africa.
Two to zero.
I watched the game at Guadalajara.
- I watched it. - I was so jealous.
- What a braggart. - Hyun Moo,
did you watch Mexico's first game?
I watched it with Mexicans in the square.
(He watched it in a square in Guadalajara.)
(People cheered passionately in Mexico.)
The photos you uploaded...
were just selfies with celebrities.
- Why did you watch it with aespa? - Really?
- Why? - Did you go there with aespa?
Can't I watch the game with aespa?
They're juniors in your agency.
- Really? - I want them on I Live Alone.
- Same here. - Same here.
You looked at me for the very first time.
It was the first time he made eye contact.
I'm sure the viewers are as curious as I am.
You met my eye for the first time, okay?
(Really?)
It's a festival for people around the world.
It's the day of the game between Korea and Czechia.
Mexico and South Africa are...
in the same group as Korea.
So we must pay attention to that game as well.
I watched it because I had to.
(The quick man who transforms in the field)
That's it!
- Yes! - He is good.
(The man who is crazy about soccer)
(Besiktas!)
(They're good at soccer.)
(He is watching Erling Haaland's game.)
- He loves soccer. - CODE KUNST is a huge fan.
(The Rainbow Club's soccer expert)
Lingard.
I wait eight years.
As I wait four years, I wait for the next World Soccer Games.
To be honest, I've lived for this day.
North and Central America has a major time difference,
so I've adjusted my body for two months.
To watch the games?
- You act like you're playing. - That was why you woke up early.
(Shall I get ready to root for the team?)
His house is clean.
(Throwing)
How many uniforms are there?
Oh, my.
(Spreading)
Gue Sung.
- Our member. - That's his uniform.
Hee Chan.
I only got the uniforms of the world-class players.
- That's a gauge. - Yes.
- A gauge for world-class players. - A gauge for world-class players.
Gosh, this is it.
Lee Young Pyo.
- Young Pyo. He is my friend. - That's incredible.
Lee Young Pyo actually wore this uniform.
- Was that a match-worn jersey? - He actually wore it.
- Gosh, that's precious. - He actually wore it?
- How did you get that? - He gave it to me as a gift.
- Really? - He gave it to you himself?
What about me?
(Desperate)
We had an opportunity to meet.
We ate together.
He knew I was a soccer fan, so he prepared that for me.
- I'm jealous. - That's a family treasure.
- That's a family treasure. - That's a family treasure.
This is my treasure.
(He spreads out his other jerseys.)
(Impressed)
- Lee Young Pyo and Park Ji Sung. - Park Ji Sung!
That was remade recently.
- Right. It was remade. - It was remade.
Can you tell just by looking at that?
- Yes. - Yes. I can tell right away.
Gosh, number 21.
- It brings back memories. - Right.
(I must take a picture of this.)
Oh, yes!
- Oh, yes! - He looks so happy.
(Happy)
(I can't leave out the cheering items.)
- He has those prepared as well? - He's fully equipped.
That's the standard set for those who like soccer.
- It's the standard form. - I see.
(He transforms into a Red Devil instantly with the basic items.)
- The vuvuzela. - That one is for daily use.
(He checks the sound of the vuvuzela as well.)
I'll need this...
and this.
(He diligently packs various cheering items.)
On top of this,
(CODE KUNST is fully dressed in black.)
I'll wear this today.
(Fitting in)
(A jersey with CODE KUNST in the back)
It's "CODE KUNST!"
- Nice. - You have that?
(Checking here and there)
Okay!
I look like a soccer freak.
(Greatly satisfied)
(He quickly gets ready to leave...)
(after being satisfied with his look.)
- He's actually leaving. - He's actually leaving.
- Yes. - Are you watching the game outside?
That day, people watched the match on the streets of Gwanghwamun Gate.
- Right. - Many people came out.
Is he going out to the streets?
If he's fully equipped like that,
- Did he go to Gwanghwamun Gate? - he should go to Gwanghwamun Gate.
- Right. - Right.
All right.
(Do well to protect the house, Panda.)
(Have a good time.)
(Singing)
- Gosh. - Why am I stuck at that song?
Why didn't you sing "Kick It?"
(Released in 2002)
(While singing cheer songs of his memories,)
(he excitedly heads somewhere.)
(I will be with you)
This song speaks to me.
It's a nice song.
You feel a bit emotional as you sing it.
- Right. - Right.
(Hey!)
It should be done with the car horn.
That was how it was done.
- Is that 2002? - Gosh!
(Everyone in the country was a Red Devil.)
I did that as well.
I went on top of some guy's car.
Right. People went on top of buses.
Weren't you all kids in 2002?
I was in middle school.
- I was 20. - I was in elementary school.
- I was a high school senior. - I was in eighth grade.
- I was in college. - You were in eighth grade?
- I was in eighth grade. - I was in middle school.
(You were in 8th grade in 2002?)
- How old are you? - Where did you watch the games?
- I was born in 1988. - What?
That's amazing.
- Where did you watch the games? - I was born in 1988.
I actually watched the game in Incheon.
- You actually watched it? - The match against Portugal...
when Park Ji Sung scored.
- I was there. - The Munhak Stadium?
- Right. I watched it there. - Really?
(He witnessed the historical moment.)
(Living witness of history, young Hyun Moo)
I'm not sure if you all will remember those times.
Right before my eyes,
- a car accident happened. - Right.
- Bam! - Gosh!
- "Just go." - Right.
- Right. - Right.
Food was free in most restaurants.
- Everything was free. - Right.
(Korea's first win in World Soccer Games! Free jjajangmyeon)
(Everyone shared the joy of victory without any conditions.)
- Korea's happiest moment. - Right.
The vibes were amazing back then.
(Although 24 years have passed after that moment,)
(Korea's matchday is always exciting.)
While living my life,
I'm someone who doesn't feel that upset about something...
or that happy about something.
This is the only thing that makes me feel excited.
Soccer is...
Sung Woo loves soccer.
It's a moment that comes every four years.
We can be as loud as we want.
It's perfectly soundproof as well.
I came to my studio.
Oh, your studio?
No one will hear anything no matter how loud I am.
- I see. - That's why you're going there.
(Looking around)
Why can't I see any red shirts?
- There wasn't a single red shirt. - Right.
I used to see 1 or 2 red shirts...
- in the past. - Right.
- There should be a few. - That was around...
- one hour before the match. - It's much different now.
- It's not like the past these days. - There should be a few then.
- The match was in the morning. - Right.
Emergency!
There should be a little bit of red.
Everyone is wearing black.
I thought to myself, "What's going on?"
It usually started a week before the World Soccer Games.
Right.
It was when I was a 7th-grader in 2002.
There was a very tough man...
in our apartment complex.
When Korea made it to the semifinals,
he smashed his own car.
He let the young ones smash his car.
"You can smash my car."
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- Right. I remember those times. - I remember those times.
(The night of madness in 2002 forgave everything.)
Everything was forgivable.
Red jerseys started to appear.
You could feel festival vibes...
starting to emerge.
(Festival vibes)
(Any religion, including the church and temple)
(Any place, including a funeral hall)
- The funeral hall! - The funeral hall!
That was hilarious.
(Everyone enjoyed 2002 with the same heart.)
This brings back so many memories.
(The memories of those times cannot be forgotten.)
- It was a miracle. - That moment will never come again.
It will never come.
It's the only thing we can boast about...
to the young ones.
I wasn't able to feel that this year.
Even on the day of the match,
it felt like I was the only one on earth to wear a red jersey.
I wondered for a while if the match was at 10pm.
(Laughing)
(Flustered)
Since there wasn't a single red shirt,
- you must've doubted yourself. - I didn't see a single red shirt.
- Right. - Not even one.
(He arrives feeling a lot of worry.)
I feel a bit embarrassed.
It feels like I'm the only one excited.
People might've thought you have come to sell things.
(Both hands are filled with cheering items.)
(Looking around)
(Why isn't there a single red shirt?)
Why is it so empty?
- There isn't a single one. - This is strange.
It was a lot different from the past.
Hello.
Welcome!
It's a chicken place that I went past often.
After seeing the chicken place open in the morning,
I realized it was matchday.
It was actually the day of the soccer festival.
- Right. They open on matchdays. - Right.
It's matchday today, right?
- Right. - This isn't our opening hours,
but we got a lot of calls.
- You got a lot of calls? - Yes.
I was the only one in a red shirt on the street.
I felt a bit embarrassed.
Will you take a look at the menu?
The garlic rotisserie chicken, soy sauce chicken,
and the soup tteokbokki.
That sounds good.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Enjoy the food.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Enjoy the food. - Thank you.
(He heads to his studio with both hands filled with chicken.)
That must taste great.
I leave some seasoned chicken the day before the match.
On purpose. Right.
- I always leave some. - Right. Chicken and rice.
- The meat should be separated. - Of course.
(He arrives at his studio with morning chicken.)
Okay.
(The studio is already open.)
(Chuckling)
Yo!
(I'm here.)
- There are people there already. - There are people there already.
- Who are they? - Who are they?
(Who has come?)
Yo!
(I'm here.)
- There are people there already. - There are people there already.
- Who are they? - Who are they?
- We brought some coffee. - It's the members of Epik High.
(Mithra, Tukutz, Tablo)
The members of Epik High!
- Epik High! - The legends!
(They have an impressive list of awards.)
(They made their debut in 2003...)
(and have an unrivaled musicality that is loved by all generations.)
(Korea's representative hip-hop group, Epik High)
When I first started making music,
they were the first ones to notice my potential.
They gave me the opportunity to make music.
They helped me so much.
A few of the instruments here...
were used by Tukutz...
and given to me as gifts.
(That's awesome.)
They're the ones you feel grateful for.
It's the same in the comedy world.
There are props that seniors like...
- Shim Hyung Rae used. - Right.
They feel different.
- It gives you confidence. - Those are hard to find as well.
- Right. - Did you get things from Oh Jae Mi?
The passwords they used or the Wi-Fi system.
None of the passwords were changed at all.
Nothing has changed from their time here.
It's just a bit cleaner than before.
I kept everything the same because of them.
(When CODE KUNST was buying the chicken...)
(Yawning)
(A Red Devil came and pressed the passcode naturally.)
- That was why they were inside. - Right.
I told him to change the batteries.
(Laughing)
They must feel upset if you change the passcode.
(The other two members arrive a while later.)
- This place feels familiar. - Doesn't it feel like home?
- What? - Our card bills still come here.
The card bills are sent there?
- What? - Tablo!
Why are you wearing black?
- What? - Why wear a black shirt?
Right. It's the day of the match.
Well...
Mithra definitely would've felt...
- guilty inside. - Right.
But he would've thought, "I'm still wearing a similar color."
As it's a similar shade.
- I'm 100 percent certain. - Right.
That's why he's staying quiet.
(Tablo is the only one in a different shade.)
- Come on. - We must all become Red Devils.
Isn't it fine if my heart is a Red Devil?
Today, you have to be a Red Devil outside.
(Tablo's outfit is disappointing.)
I brought some jerseys.
- Lend me one then. - Right.
- Did you bring theirs? - That was why I brought a few.
I don't know a lot about soccer.
I just watch the World Soccer Games.
- That's the best. - It's Park Ji Sung's jersey!
(It's Park Ji Sung's jersey!)
- Tablo should wear it then. - Right.
Right.
He used to be known for looking like Park Ji Sung.
- Right. - Park Ji Sung.
- Right. - Right.
- He was known for that. - Right.
Here you are.
(Here you are, Park Ji Sung.)
- "Here you are." - You asked why I brought them.
Now, you look the most interested.
- Yes! - He loves it.
(Excited)
- It's different with a jersey on. - Think about it.
- Right. - Imagine going to a game...
in a regular outfit.
- That can't happen. - Your heart won't click.
- It won't match the vibe. - You must follow the dress code.
Why are you wearing so many layers indoors?
It's cold here.
It fits you a lot better than I thought.
I'm not fat!
It's a stereotype that people have about me.
People have a misunderstanding that I'm really big.
- He lost a lot of weight. - He said he lost a lot of weight.
(He shows off the cheering items he brought from home.)
(Blowing)
Don't blow that.
(Laughing)
Did you hear me?
I was going to watch it quietly at home.
You can't do that.
Soccer must be watched with a lot of noise.
- It must be loud with soccer. - Right.
Soccer must be watched in a wild atmosphere.
That's a great line. "Soccer must be watched with a lot of noise."
I can't click with you right now.
That means he wants me to blow it one more time.
(Blowing)
Are you sure?
I've spent a lot of time with them.
You understand the Epik High language?
Right.
Don't blow that.
(Just enjoy it.)
"Please blow it."
(Translation)
(Blowing)
What is that? Is that a vuvuzela?
- Give me one. - See?
Why would you blow that indoors?
Isn't he a representative celebrity soccer freak?
You're going to watch Park Ji Sung's commentary, right?
Of course.
(Of course.)
He's watching himself.
(The Park Ji Sung lookalike confidently takes his seat.)
Power!
I gave it to Tukutz.
- It's mine. - Gosh, it looks nice.
Is this the one G-DRAGON made?
(Limited edition jacket collaborated with GD)
I want to wear that.
Power!
I gave it to Tukutz.
No! Give it to me if it was made by G-DRAGON.
It's mine!
We heard, "It's mine!"
You're not actually giving it to him, right?
I am.
He looks so excited.
That's hard to get.
(You're not actually giving it to him, right?)
(I am.)
- Well... - We gave you this TV.
- So... - "We?" I bought it.
- I bought this TV. - I bought it.
- I bought it. - It's mine.
- I bought it for you! - I bought it!
- Wait. - It's mine.
Get out your receipt.
- I bought it for you. - You bought it?
- They're so childish. - Fourth-graders!
They're just like fourth-graders.
Are they fathers of children or children?
(Confused)
- You bought it? - Gosh!
Get out your receipt.
- I bought it for you! - You bought it?
I bought this for you as a gift...
for coming into this studio.
Gosh. I should never buy things...
- for a friend. - He got it back from him.
Hey, did I leave that fridge for you?
Yes.
CODE KUNST gave the jacket to Tablo.
It should be given to the one who bought the TV.
- Hey. - Tablo was the one to buy it.
But how can you take it away from him?
The one who gave the TV deserves it.
It must be done accurately.
- His lips are drooping down. - Tablo...
- His lips are dropping down! - He's upset!
Take it if you want, Jeong Sik.
You love G-DRAGON.
- It's fine. - This won't be released again.
Gosh, he's going to be upset.
- I'll give it to you. - Give it to him.
Gosh.
- Gosh. - Power!
- His lips are going up! - His lips are going up!
- His lips! - They're going up!
Why get upset?
- He's going to sing, "Power!" - He went, "Power!"
(Home sweet home)
(You were all wrong.)
- SIK-DRAGON. - SIK-DRAGON.
(JEONG SIK-DRAGON)
They're hilarious.
- We should have some chicken. - Let's set the table.
We can't eat before the match starts.
We should eat when the match starts.
- Why is that? - What?
- Why is that? - Why is that?
- Why is that? The food is there. - That's...
A box of chicken must be eaten before the match starts.
Right. It should be eaten like an energy bar.
Enough is enough.
(Enough is enough in front of the chicken.)
Whenever I buy food,
whether it be for a movie, soccer match, or a concert,
they finish everything before it starts.
- That's how it is. - That's how it is.
That's what people usually do.
The popcorn must be eaten when it's hot.
But since that always happened,
I wanted to eat the food while watching the match.
Why must that happen?
I wanted to talk with them before the match.
Why eat after the match starts?
(Grumbling)
He's grumbling.
- See? - He sounds like my grandpa.
You should have some sauce around your mouth.
I was wrong, wasn't I?
- You were wrong. - You were wrong.
- It's flowing that way. - Right.
- You can't do that. - Right.
- You must eat right away. - You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
We can't eat...
- before the kick-off? - We can't.
Even before a movie starts,
- I finish the popcorn. - Hey, let's eat.
- It's time for me to eat. - Well...
(Sensitive)
(Smacking his lips)
- Hey! - Prepare the next thing.
The food is going to go bad after 30 minutes.
Then let's open one box.
There was tteokbokki now that I think about it.
We should eat the tteokbokki as well.
- Hey. - We won't eat the chicken?
We can't eat the chicken?
(A bolt from the blue)
- Gosh, he's so exhausting. - CODE KUNST is a bit...
I don't like this place.
- It must be his superstition. - I have a superstition as well.
I don't like watching a game like this.
We'll lose if we do this.
(Let's cheer our team for 30 minutes.)
Go, Korea!
(Go, Korea!)
Look at Mithra!
(It's loud and he feels hungry.)
Don't you have earplugs at the studio?
It must be like this when watching soccer.
He's genuinely prepared to watch the soccer match.
I live for this.
I'm not joking about this.
- I always wait for this event. - I'm always like that.
What are you saying? You didn't even know there was a match today.
Why are there only three?
I came from abroad yesterday to watch this here!
- Really? - It was to watch this here!
You asked if the games started in September.
Gosh, I feel so annoyed.
They get on each other's nerves so well.
- When did I say that? - Let's take turns to take shots.
(They're already fighting again.)
It's actually the World Soccer Games.
I want to watch it live.
During the 2002 games,
I watched the France versus Senegal match...
- Hold on. - at the stadium.
Really?
Did you watch the 2002 games at home?
- I watched it at the academy. - The academy?
The English academy.
(Gosh, you're a baby.)
- Gosh, you snot-nosed kid. - Gosh.
Hey, we watched it while drinking beer in Sinchon.
(Distant memory)
I'm really jealous.
I'm really jealous...
- that they were adults in 2002. - Right.
- Right. - Right.
I have a question. What's your score prediction?
I predict a 3:0 win.
- A 3:0 win? - A 3:0 win?
I'm serious about this.
- I think it will be a 5:1 win. - A 5:1 win?
- A 5:1 win. - I think it will be a 4:1 win.
Korea 4, Czech Republic 1.
Gosh.
Those were terrible predictions.
- But... - Hyun Moo's prediction.
But, Hyun Moo...
(The one who predicted the 2:1 turnaround win feels relaxed.)
Do you know why I predicted a 3:0 win?
It's fun to make a big bet.
- Right. - I'm not interested about bets.
I could see 2:1 in my eyes.
- Sorry? What are you saying? - Gosh.
On top of that, I predicted the exact score...
and I guessed that Oh Hyeon Gyu would score.
Really?
My nickname is Shaman Jun Hyun Moo right now.
I'm serious.
- What about the Mexico game? - The next one.
Right. We'll admit it if you get this one right.
- Here's Shaman Jun Hyun Moo. - Shaman Jun Hyun Moo.
All right.
My first prediction was 2:2.
- Which team was 2? - I predicted 2:2.
- Oh, 2:2. - I see.
But Mexico's Kim Min Jae got sent off.
He can't play against Korea.
That is why I predict it will be a 2:1 win.
- A 2:1 win? - Korea will win 2:1.
- It was actually 2:2? - Right.
What about the scorer of the first goal?
Must we go in that deep?
You guessed Oh Hyeon Gyu right.
You said you saw it with your eyes.
Tell us what you see.
- Actually, - Through Shaman Jun's eyes.
- I see Cho Gue Sung. - Cho Gue Sung?
There aren't many tall players in the Mexican team,
so Cho Gue Sung might be used.
- As a starting member? - In the second half.
- It sounds convincing. - Oh, in the second half?
- In the 2nd half. - In the 2nd half.
Then will Korea score first?
- I can't see about that. - You can't?
There are things that even shamans can't see.
- What are you talking about? - That's so convenient.
(Unfortunately, he failed to predict the result.)
Even just the talk about it makes us excited.
- I know. - I know. Me too.
Then let's bet on the specifics.
The first goal from Korea.
I think it'll be from Lee Kang In.
No.
What do you mean no? I think he'll score.
The first goal...
will be from Hwang In Beom.
That sounds possible.
This is the difference between...
a knowledgeable fan and a clueless fan.
Son Heung Min and Lee Kang In...
- are a pair. - That's right.
- Only the players. - The current lineup is the best.
Let's go.
(Everyone gets up.)
- Let's go. - Gosh, the national anthem.
- When the song plays, - With deep respect.
everyone listens with deep respect.
This is a must.
- It makes you excited. - Five to one.
Three to zero.
The mecca of street cheering.
(A sea of red gathered at Gwanghwamun Square as one.)
(Let's go, Korea!)
(Clapping)
(The four gathered at a different place but with the same heart.)
- Two to one. - Okay.
(5 minutes before the game starts)
I have a good feeling, though.
- Yes. - It's not bad, right?
- I have a good feeling. - Seeing how the coach...
has the same hairstyle as mine, I think it's going to go well.
- They do look similar. - They look similar.
- You know that feeling. - I have a good feeling.
When the coaches had...
similar hairstyles as Tukutz for the World Soccer Games,
Korea always did well.
There's such a belief?
Are they playing?
- Hold on. - Number 19.
- Number 19. - He lifted it.
- He's playing. - I can eat...
as soon as they kick off, right?
- Yes. - I can get ready ahead, right?
That's right.
It's Paik Seung Ho.
But you can't put it in your mouth.
All right.
(Come on.)
My goodness.
This is the fun part. The fun part has started.
(Shameless)
- Is it okay if my spit gets on it? - No.
My younger brother, have a bite first.
- You can't taste it. - As soon as they kick off...
- It's started. - They can eat now.
(The first half has started.)
Take a bite.
It's started. You can eat now.
(Taking a big bite)
You see? Something fun happens if you wait.
This is really fun.
It does look fun because you ate after the whistle.
It must be more delicious since they were starved.
(They finally taste the fried chicken after the match started.)
Are you on the winning side or the losing side...
when you cheer for your team?
- When I cheer for them, - They lose.
they lose for sure.
We're done for.
But when the three of us gathered and watched, they always won.
- Is that so? - When three of us meet, they win.
I'm mostly on the winning side too.
- They're warmed up. - Actually, when we watched,
they always scored when I went to the bathroom.
That's true.
There are people who claim the team loses...
- when they watch the game. - That's right.
- I had one big incident, though. - What is it?
During the match against Italy in the 2002 World Soccer Game,
I turned around and left when I thought they lost.
But Seol Ki Hyeon...
- score the equalizer. - The equalizer.
You shouldn't watch then.
- I shouldn't watch? - He shouldn't watch?
Please sleep during the match against Mexico.
Seon Min, please sleep.
- Yes, please go crash. - Just sleep.
You should go to sleep.
Let's go.
- It's Seol Young Woo, right? - Let's score directly from a cross.
(They continue to chew with their eyes fixed on the TV.)
It doesn't look bad, though. I think Team Korea is more agile.
- We have better energy. - I know.
Why can't we see the match, though?
We can't watch the match because of copyright restrictions.
You should watch while imagining the game.
You guys can play it in your head, can't you?
The Czech team...
- is physically strong. - It's a bummer.
- They're strong. - They're tall too.
Their average height is 190cm.
I wonder how it'd feel to live as a tall person like him.
They say it's inconvenient.
It's inconvenient.
- Their knees hurt too. - I bet it's inconvenient...
- on planes. - Of course.
Their knees hurt too.
I hope they fall.
- That's so... - That's blunt.
It's really blunt and simple.
I get where that comes from.
Also, it's important to cheer like that.
- I've seen worse. - For me, when I watch the game,
I do this instead of talking.
When the ball goes over the goal line,
or when I wish it to go over the line,
I'd suck in the air like this.
Like this.
- So the ball goes over the line? - When I wish it...
to go the other way,
I do this.
(That's right.)
But it's sort of effective.
- What? It works? - Yes, it works for real.
- Your energy is sent. - My energy is sent.
My gosh.
It actually works. Try it.
That's so like MINHO.
They should score one now if they're to score five.
- What? - What?
Hey, that's... That one's going in!
- Here we go. - Wait, they're almost there!
- It's going in! - Goal!
Gosh!
What a loss!
Someone should've been standing there!
(Someone should've been standing there!)
You become a coach when you watch a game.
Everyone becomes a coach when you watch it from home.
- You'd point at them too. - This is hilarious.
- Hey! - What was that?
- That's right. - The referee didn't give a foul.
A foul.
- Why not give a foul? - When he fell?
- Why didn't he give a foul? - It's when Lee Kang In fell, right?
- He basically threw him. - The situation like this...
We're watching them watching a soccer match.
- It's so weird. - Right.
And the viewers are watching us.
- The viewers are watching us... - Everyone is watching each other.
- It could feel frustrating. - watching CODE KUNST...
- watching a soccer game. - It's so weird.
It's a three-layer watching.
The viewers are watching us watching the three of them...
watching a game.
What on earth is happening?
(A third-level observer's viewpoint?)
- Why? Why not give a foul? - What? Why didn't he give a foul?
He basically threw him.
- To the outside... - Referee, move!
I didn't like that jerk from the start.
(Embarrassed)
That's the most one-dimensional.
It's blind criticism.
- "I knew you'd be like that." - Right.
"I knew you'd be like that."
- We got it. - Good!
It's going in! This one's going in!
- Tablo... - Shoot!
Shoot!
Someone should be waiting at the back!
- We got it! - Gosh, Mithra.
- Yellow card! - Red card.
- Is it okay to push like that? - How can he push Kang In...
- Doesn't that deserve a red card? - That's not right.
He pushed.
A death sentence for you.
A death sentence?
- A death sentence. - He can get ahead.
- A death sentence? - Yes.
- Sir, that's a bit... Yes. - No?
That's not exactly illegal.
The first-ever death sentence.
I think he deserves at least five years in prison.
(Lenient)
- A death sentence was too much. - Right?
Let's get a shot on target, at least.
Gosh, let's rest for a bit.
- Gosh, seriously. - Gosh, seriously.
Darn it!
Gosh, the first half...
Are you serious?
I'm so sad.
We started the game well.
We lost the momentum right away.
We did all the reactions that middle-aged men would do.
Darn it.
(Half-time)
We can finally see the screen.
(Feeling relieved)
- It was frustrating. - You're right.
(They give a break of cheering during half-time.)
How come I see no spiders this year?
It's about time I see one.
- A spider? The long one? - Yes.
- Why do I not see it? - Don't catch it when you see one.
Why not?
They eat all the harmful insects.
But there are so many of them that they feel like harmful insects.
- You shouldn't catch a spider. - Don't catch a spider.
That's why there were so many spiders there.
- I see. - Right.
I don't catch money bugs.
- Me neither. - Money bugs?
I don't catch money bugs smaller than this.
Then you should give a few spiders to Seon Min.
You should send some spiders to him.
Shall we exchange?
(Exchange money bugs for spiders)
- Exchange goods for goods. - That's right.
- With cockroaches... That's right. - We need to control the population.
- Then I... - You need to exchange.
I'll give you my spiders.
That's the Korean hospitality.
(Let's share the bug pets we have.)
When I was working, a cricket...
- came down from the ceiling. - Inside the studio?
- Yes. - I close all the windows.
It's starting.
(The second half begins.)
Come on.
My gosh.
- Tukutz, it's been... - It's like...
ten seconds only.
- But... - What?
(The armchair coaches are starting again.)
He's pushing!
Hey, you shouldn't have come out.
The first half ended in a draw,
so everyone is sensitive.
But that's... It shouldn't go like that.
- They need to step up. - I need to go to the bathroom.
I've been holding it for a while.
Why didn't you go during the break?
- Why go when the game's started? - Exactly.
- You always do that. - I must've had too much chicken.
- Go ahead. - The problem is...
I can't go because I feel like they will score while I use the bathroom.
- Let's go. Please score just one. - You guys would roar.
They couldn't score when they were playing so well.
Let's get a goal.
- Please score one. - It's going well.
That's good!
(Things seem to be going well.)
The two of you don't even know who they are.
- They scored? - They scored.
(The Czech team took the lead from a throw-in situation.)
With just one goal like that, you lose all the energy.
That's a photo, right?
- Yes. - A photo.
It's a photo. We know the situation.
- We know. - Watching a game like this...
- is so refreshing. - I know.
Next time, there will be a drawing.
Or sand art?
(Or sand art?)
- Like a sand animation? - Yes.
(Let's make a video of their shot.)
(AI-generated video)
(Republic of Korea: 0, Czech Republic: 1)
(Due to an unexpected goal from the other team...)
This is crazy.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
You feel deflated when they score early in the second half.
- I know. - Yes, you feel deflated.
Our team was pushing forward too.
- Yes, we were. - I know.
It's okay. It's better this way.
We're better at catching up.
It's okay.
While we were pushing forward...
It ruined my mood all of a sudden.
Actually, it was devastating.
- I know. - It was devastating.
It was the second half, that's why.
- Right. - It felt like...
- we didn't have enough time. - Right.
The game doesn't go well if the players feel rushed.
This is what moved me so much when I was there.
Whether they were Mexicans or Koreans,
- Everyone. - they were all cheering for Korea.
Every Mexican and Korean around me...
went, "Go Korea!" They were all cheering for Korea.
- "Korea!" - Is that because of K-pop?
- Or because Korea helped before? - K-pop...
During the Russia Soccer Game, Mexico advanced...
- to the Round of 16 thanks to us. - That's right.
- Because we beat Germany, - That's right.
- they think of us as brothers. - It's like...
But when the Czech team scored after a long throw-in...
It was a tap-in goal.
Krejci scored with a header.
- Everyone went silent then. - That's right.
Only those who were there would know this kind of information.
It became silent for a moment.
I couldn't speak because it was such a letdown.
Because you're sharing the story from the stadium,
- I feel like I'm there right now. - I know.
- It's really different. - Can you keep sharing?
- He's indeed a commentator. - Hyun Moo, please keep going.
- I want to listen. - I'll tell you how it was there.
It feels like the scene is unfolding.
I think this flooring helps too.
- You're right. - This flooring.
- It's grass. - Right. It's Guadalajara grass.
(From the stadium)
Fine.
This won't do. I really wasn't going to use this trick.
I should go to the bathroom.
- I'll just... - The bathroom!
That's right. Go to the bathroom when the game doesn't do well.
- Hurry up and go so they score. - He should hurry up and go.
- There's no chance. - Hey.
- There's no chance. - But they're pressuring us more.
They're not playing safe.
- Darn. - Darn it.
This won't do.
We need to cheer.
(They start cheering again to change the momentum.)
Go, Korea!
It was like that at the stadium too.
- I guess it's the same. - Go, Korea!
- It's the same. - It's the same. It was the same.
- When will he play? - Wait.
(The level of their voices is rising.)
- That's it! - Oh, it's then.
Seriously.
(Hwang In Beom's dramatic equalizer)
(Shaking thanks to the thrilling equalizer)
You see?
Hey.
- He missed it. He was right. - Is this for real?
They scored when he was gone.
- Lock him up! - Lock him up in the bathroom.
- Gosh, this actually worked? - Lock him up in the bathroom.
Lock Tablo up in the bathroom.
(They scored as soon as Tablo left for the bathroom.)
Gosh, thank you, Tablo.
They scored thanks to Tablo.
- No way. - Lock him up. He can't come out.
- They scored. - What happened?
- They scored? - Hwang In Beom.
(Cheering)
(Making a fuss)
Replay! I missed it!
No, go back in there.
- Go back in there. - Go!
- I missed it. - Hurry up and go back in.
You see? Hwang In Beom scored.
- I know. - Hwang In Beom.
This is what made me happy the most.
The soccer-loving fans...
like guessing who would score.
Mithra and I guessed...
that Hwang In Beom would score.
The first goal...
- Hwang In Beom? - will be from Hwang In Beom.
- That sounds possible. - You guessed correctly.
In terms of probability only.
You're so smart.
I wondered if that's how Lee Young Pyo feels.
Will I become CODE KUNST the Octopus?
- That's what I thought. - How about TACO?
- TACO KUNST sounds good. - TACO KUNST.
Did you see that? They scored as soon as we started cheering.
Didn't they score as soon as I went to the bathroom?
- Everyone is taking the credit. - This is amazing.
You have the key, right?
- Lock him up. - I knew it.
- I knew Hwang In Beom would score. - I knew Hwang In Beom would score.
- This really doesn't make sense. - Look.
(CODE KUNST the Octopus's guess was spot on.)
- A chip shot from here. - It was amazing.
He could score because Son Heung Min and Lee Kang In were there.
- That's true. - Of course.
(The atmosphere is electric.)
How was it when you saw him score at the stadium?
At the stadium, I saw him score from my place.
Hwang In Beom was going like this.
- It's Hwang In Beom! - He turned and...
- I can imagine it. - Jun In Beom!
- He came with two defenders. - Jun In Beom?
- Jun In Beom. - Then he scored like this.
But that shot...
looked really slow from where I was.
(So...)
(what happened next?)
The ball rolled away, so I thought the defender would kick it.
I was like this.
- But it rolled in. - That's right.
(Moved)
Gosh, you're amazing. You're a good storyteller.
I found the strength of your commentary.
- What is it? - You make sound effects like this.
Something like, "rolling."
- "Rolling." - "Rolling."
And it feels like I'm there.
At the stadium, the ball seemed to be moving slowly.
- The speed. - Please don't stop.
- Like a narrated fairy tale. - Yes, a narrated fairy tale.
When the ball went in,
people started roaring from far.
(Cheering)
(An uncanny reenactment)
- Hyun Moo, share it like that. - The roar...
The roar echoed over like a surround sound system.
Do that when you commentate too.
- The sound... - Only the Czech team was quiet.
You're even describing the sound that gets gradually loud.
Hyun Moo, I respect you.
It's like he's telling a story from the Korean War.
Like a grandmother would.
We'll see the photo again after listening to your story.
We'll see the photo now.
He'll commentate before we see the photo.
Hey, the momentum has shifted.
It's getting fun.
- We got it now. - It's getting fun.
I win if Team Korea scores three more.
I knew it'd be Hwang In Beom.
He was really calm.
Why do I miss it every time?
You were like this in the bathroom.
Seriously, I...
It's scary!
- It's legendary. - "They scored?"
He came out after cleaning himself up, right?
Why did you come out again? Stay in the bathroom.
It's not that. I'll go there when there's a crisis.
I can't stay in there forever.
You can't do that for the World Soccer Game?
If our team faces a crisis again,
- I'll go to the bathroom. - Okay.
Please go again if they don't score until the 40th minute.
- I'll go again. - No, the 37th minute.
I'll keep eating. Don't worry.
- I need to fuel up. - This is fun.
Let's go.
(The momentum has shifted already.)
From then on, Team Korea picked up the momentum.
Gosh, no.
(However...)
I knew that'd happen.
(They conceded from a set piece again.)
- That's when... - My heart dropped then.
- Back then... - Everyone went silent again then.
I knew that'd happen.
- It's offside! - It's offside!
(The goal was disallowed for offside.)
It's offside!
He totally went ahead.
- Hey. - Hey, look, you punk.
- You punk! - You brat.
- It's offside. - Hey!
- You little brat. - You're so impatient.
It was totally...
Gosh, I'm so glad.
(Relieved for real)
We change our stances so fast.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
(34th minute of 2nd half, Republic of Korea: 1, Czech Republic: 1)"
We have three minutes now.
Can you make the scoreboard with sand art?
Anything is possible with sand art.
- With sand art? - We can get all the details too.
- With sand art? - Yes.
Then to express the 34th minute, you should do this with sand.
- Like this. Anything is possible. - It's like a treasure hunt.
- Can you draw the audience too? - Of course. Anything is possible.
(34th minute of 2nd half, Republic of Korea: 1, Czech Republic: 1)
Time for Tablo to go to the bathroom.
It's the 34th minute.
You should go back in there if they don't score within three minutes.
- When should I go to the bathroom? - At the 37th minute.
- It's decided. - Darn it.
Don't watch the game on your phone in there.
My goodness.
You shouldn't be watching.
- Do something else. - I don't want to go again.
(Wait.)
- We got it. - We got it!
- That's it. Oh Hyeon Gyu! - Oh Hyeon Gyu!
(Oh Hyeon Gyu's equalizer)
- We got it. - We got it!
(Shouting out the thrill of a comeback goal)
Gosh, he's crying.
- CODE KUNST! - He's crying.
Gosh, TACO KUNST.
I almost cried too, CODE KUNST.
I was really overwhelmed.
I almost cried too.
Everyone was overwhelmed by this.
It was my first time to cry while watching soccer.
- Really? - Being there made me cry.
It feels different at the stadium.
While I was cheering, a tear dropped.
It's the pride you have...
- for your country too. - That's right.
You'd feel more patriotic because you're in another country.
- Oh Hyeon Gyu. - Oh Hyeon Gyu!
- Oh Hyeon Gyu! I guessed right. - Oh Hyeon Gyu!
Gosh, Sir TACO KUNST.
I wish Oh Hyeon Gyu would score.
(CODE KUNST the Octopus is indeed amazing.)
(Dancing)
(Playing the saxophone with all his might...)
(to express how moved he is with the comeback goal)
You can't play that. Put it down.
That was perfect.
It's so funny.
- Be careful. - Hey!
No.
Kim Seung Gyu!
(Cheering)
- Kim Seung Gyu's save. - Kim Seung Gyu.
- Kim Seung Gyu. - It was amazing.
This one was incredible.
- How did he save it, really? - This one was dangerous.
- It went out. - We need to reward the goalkeeper.
We need to reward the goalkeeper?
- I haven't heard that in a while. - Gosh, Kim Seung Gyu.
- Seriously. - A prize.
Let's really give the goalkeeper an award.
- What a folksy expression. - That's folksy.
It's folksy.
(Rewarding him with clapping)
How did he save that, seriously?
That player is...
It's even more amazing than scoring.
Of course. Kim Seung Gyu...
They just need to hold out a little more.
Now that we're at it, let's score two more.
- Yes. Let's make it 4 to 1. - They need to keep pushing.
I can't believe they caught up like that all of a sudden.
I know.
(Right then, the Czech player appeals to the referee about pain.)
What's wrong with him?
Just bear with it! You're a professional athlete.
(He's reliable.)
You play soccer with your feet, not your face!
(Right then)
(The Czech team is threatening the goal again.)
That time. It was really hard.
- It's dangerous. - No!
(No!)
- No! - No.
(Brilliant Seung Gyu saves again.)
- Seung Gyu! - Brilliant Seung Gyu.
- Kim Seung Gyu is amazing. - Brilliant Seung Gyu.
- You should put on shades... - Gosh, Kim Seung Gyu.
- because he's too brilliant. - He is amazing.
- Yes. - Brilliant Seung Gyu.
(Relieved)
We need to give an award to the goalkeeper!
Applaud.
I've never seen CODE KUNST so immersed like this.
Does anyone know his address?
- I want to send him something. - He's the best.
- Kim Seung Gyu. - He's doing the work of ten.
I feel the most anxious in the last one minute and a half.
- Right. - It's the most nerve-racking.
- When you let your guard down, - That's right.
the goal goes in right away.
Do you know what I did at the stadium...
when only one minute was left?
I got up.
It's a heroic story.
"One minute!"
Every Mexican and Korean...
- "One minute!" - shouted, "One minute!"
- Even the Mexicans? - Saying there's one minute left.
- You led the cheer? - Yes, I did.
- That's... - Gosh.
I wanted to let the players know that there's one minute left.
"There's only one minute left!"
- I see. - "Hang in there until the end."
- You had such a deep intention? - Of course.
That's really nice.
- Darn. - No!
No. Go. Go get it.
- That's it! - No!
It's more nerve-racking because it's the last one.
- It's gut-wrenching. - Kick it hard!
- End it with a pass. - We got it.
- We got it. That's it. - Yes!
(The game ends. Korea wins with a score of 2 to 1.)
(Roaring)
- Gosh. - Goodness.
It was incredible.
For the 1st time in 16 years,
- we won the 1st game. - The 1st game.
Seriously.
How do we come together...
- as one with just one ball? - Tell me about it.
Seriously.
Do you know which song was played...
at the stadium after the game?
- Which song? - A DAY6's song.
- "Time of Our Life?" - That song was played.
- Really? - So everyone sang along.
They played it for Koreans.
Oh, it meant it was the time of our life.
(Precious time of our life)
They did so well.
I thought it was worth the four years' wait.
Team Korea always lost the game I got up to watch...
with sleepy eyes at home by myself.
I think we won because we watched it together.
Their faces turned redder...
than any kids' faces.
There was a moment when our faces were as red as the uniform.
I think it was fun because I watched it with the guys.
The game was at 11am,
so I thought it wouldn't be exciting.
But I think it was even better.
"I watched a soccer game..."
"and have the whole day to savor the joy of victory?"
I felt good the whole day.
Me too. Seriously.
I think soccer is the only thing...
that can make me break the calm.
- You look the happiest. - Seriously.
My voice went hoarse for the first time in my life...
because of soccer.
It could've been my first time...
having fried chicken in the morning.
I think today will be memorable.
We're leaving.
Take this.
They left right away?
- You didn't have a party afterward? - They're leaving right away?
They went back to their daily life...
to pick up their kids from kindergarten.
I'm worried.
I'm worried CODE KUNST would ask us to watch a soccer game together...
whenever there is one.
That's what made me feel so good.
Because the team won, we promised to watch the next one together.
- Of course. - That's right.
Let's watch together again next time.
- Come to our office. - Come to our office.
We're leaving.
- Bye, guys. - See you.
(Next story)
(Feeling stiff)
(It's already noon?)
(Today is a day off.)
(I think I'm having a day off after 3 weeks.)
(A perfect day to catch up on the house chores she put off)
(Turning on the air conditioner before doing the chores)
(The lowest temperature shouldn't be 29°C.)
(The air conditioner is causing trouble from the start.)
(Still, let's start cleaning the windows...)
(for a change of mood.)
(Squeaking)
(The posture is making her hotter when it's already hot.)
(Is this a penalty or what?)
(Today is a mess.)
(But today's the only day off.)
(Let's make a proper meal for myself since I worked hard.)
(Savoring)
(Yes, this is it.)
(Let's relieve it with a bite.)
(Whether it's food or happiness, I'm the one to make it.)
(Taking a bite)
(Grabbing)
(I feel the happiest now.)
(Lucky Day)
(Big Appetite Day)
(Someone is visiting Ji Hyeon.)
(The first Rainbow Club member to visit Ji Hyeon's place,)
(CODE KUNST)
(People always tell me that I don't dress well.)
(Now, he's done with sweatpants.)
(Ji Hyeon wants to dress like a Seoulite.)
(Country mouse Ji Hyeon's aspired style, CODE KUNST)
(Let's go shopping one day.)
(It's finally their shopping day!)
(Hooray!)
(Country mouse Ji Hyeon has come to Hannam-dong...)
(where CODE KUNST lives.)
(Looking around)
(Is this a car dealership?)
(This is a concept store, right?)
(Is this a Korean brand?)
(At the thought of becoming a stylish Seoulite,)
(his heart is beating fast.)
(Just trust me!)
(The fearless touch of the style mentor)
(My goodness. I can't believe it.)
(Don't doubt it.)
(Just feel it.)
(Forget the country mouse Ji Hyeon.)
(Ji Hyeon's striking transformation)
(A style never seen before)
(My Style Coach)